[{"question": "Choose a correct statement regarding automatic variables.", "option1": "A) #include<stdio.h>\nmain()\n\n{\n\tauto int a;\n\n\tprintf(\"%d\", a);\n}\n\n//output is compiler error. a is not initialized.\n", "option2": "B) #include<stdio.h>\nmain()\n\n{\n\tauto int a;\n\n\tprintf(\"%d\", a);\n}\n\n//output = 0", "option3": "C) #include<stdio.h>\nmain()\n\n{\n\tauto int a;\n\n\tprintf(\"%d\", a);\n}\n\n//output = null", "option4": "D) #include<stdio.h>\nmain()\n\n{\n\tauto int a;\n\n\tprintf(\"%d\", a);\n}\n\n//output = some random number", "ans": "D"}, {"question": "What is the output of the program.?\n#include<stdio.h>\nint main()\n{\n\tprintf(\"Hello Boss.\");\n}\n", "option1": "A) Hello Boss.", "option2": "B) hello boss", "option3": "C) No output", "option4": "D) Compiler error", "ans": "D"}, {"question": "What is the output of the program.?\nint main()\n{\n\tauto int a=10;\n\t{\n\t\tauto int a = 15;\n\t\tprintf(\"%d \", a);\n\t}\n\tprintf(\"%d \", a);\n\treturn 1;\n}\n", "option1": "A) 10 10", "option2": "B) 10 15", "option3": "C) 15 10", "option4": "D) Compiler error", "ans": "C"}, {"question": "What is the output of the program.?\nint main()\n{\n\tregister a=10;\n\t{\n\t\tregister a = 15;\n\t\tprintf(\"%d \", a);\n\t}\n\tprintf(\"%d \", a);\n\t\n\treturn 20;\n}\n", "option1": "A) 15 20", "option2": "B) 15 10", "option3": "C) 10 15", "option4": "D) 15 15", "ans": "B"}, {"question": "What is the output of the C Program statement.?\nregister int b;\nprinf(\"%d\", b);\n", "option1": "A) null", "option2": "B) 0", "option3": "C) random integer number", "option4": "D) random real number", "ans": "C"}, {"question": "What is the output the program.?\nint main()\n{\n\tregister a=80;\n\tauto int b;\n\tb=a;\n\tprintf(\"%d \", a);\n\tprintf(\"%d \", b);\n\t\n\treturn -1;\n}\n", "option1": "A) Compiler error. You can not assign register value to int variable.", "option2": "B) 80 80", "option3": "C) 80 0\nRegister value can not be copied.", "option4": "D) Compiles, but output is none.", "ans": "B"}, {"question": "What is the output of the program.?\nvoid myshow();\n\nint main()\n{\n\tmyshow();\n\tmyshow();\n\tmyshow();\n}\n\nvoid myshow()\n{\n\tstatic int k = 20;\n\tprintf(\"%d \", k);\n\tk++;\n}\n", "option1": "A) 20 20 20", "option2": "B) 20 21 21", "option3": "C) 20 21 22", "option4": "D) Compiler error.", "ans": "C"}, {"question": "What is the output of the program.?\n#include<stdio.h>\nstatic int k;\n\nint main()\n{\n\tprintf(\"%d\", k);\n\t\n\treturn 90;\n}\n", "option1": "A) -1", "option2": "B) 0", "option3": "C) 90", "option4": "D) Compiler error", "ans": "B"}, {"question": "What is the output of the program.?\nint main()\n{\n\tregister k = 25;\n\tprintf(\"%d\", &k);\n\t\n\treturn 90;\n}\n\n", "option1": "A) prints of address of variable k.", "option2": "B) 25", "option3": "C) 0", "option4": "D) Compiler error", "ans": "D"}, {"question": " The statement below is .....a\nextern int p;\n", "option1": "A) Declaration", "option2": "B) Definition", "option3": "C) Initialization", "option4": "D) None of the above", "ans": "A"}]
